The outfit I'm going to show you today will be
great for festivals.
Everyone who loves the color violet will
fall in love again.  The neck part
has a three-dimensional design. Look how beautiful it is. I am getting a
gold-colored leggings.
It can
be said to be ankle-cut. The scarf is also
in the same color. The entire border is also gold
.  In this, we are
only provided with a top and a skirt.
I purchased the leggings separately
.  Now let's style my hair.
This is a big task. I do
n't know what to choose. I have to
try one or two or three models. So
finally, I'm applying moisturizer to my face
.  The dress has full
sleeves, which gives it a dignified look. The
hairstyle also matches well with
this dress. Now, I
would say to add a fringe to elevate your eyes. Don't forget to add a blush and
your favorite lipstick shade
.  Now, you can get ready in
two different styles, as I'm showing you
.  It would be appropriate to wear only
large earrings, complete with a
watch or bracelet, and a
scarf
.
Those who want to wear gold-colored jewelry should try this as well,
adding simple earrings to a simple neck chain to
elevate it properly.  Let's
take a look at the final look.  Whatever you
like, you
can go directly to Instagram and purchase it.
Let's meet tomorrow with a new outfit.